<?xml version="1.0"?>
<products>

<product id="1" category="Rings">
<title>3/4 ct. Princess Cut Diamond Solitaire Engagement Ring in 18k White Gold</title>
<price>999</price>
<image>ring1.jpg</image>
<stock>98</stock>
<description>Meticulously crafted in 750 Gold, this exclusive design by NATURAL DIAMOND is available to you directly from the source. The 'Matthiola' design is set with 47 diamonds, weighing 2.22 ctw. Featuring a sparkly 1.57ct center stone, graded F / VS1 natural diamond this beautiful piece is available in 14K gold, 18K gold or platinum.

Read below to learn about the quality of the main diamond:

F Color:
This F color diamond has no color visible to an untrained eye. As the least expensive diamond color in the colorless range (D-F) F color diamonds display minimal color difference from D or E color diamonds and offer a lower price.

VS1 Clarity:
This VS1 clarity diamond has few, very small inclusions. Inclusions are not visible to the unaided eye.

Round Shape:
The Round Brilliant cut diamond is the most popular diamond shape available today. In addition to being the most popular shape, a Round diamond gives you more flexibility in terms of balancing cut, color, and clarity grades while still getting the fire and brilliance you want.

EGL Certificate:
EGL certificates are recognized around the globe for their accuracy and integrity, defining industry standards in evaluation and appraisal. The company maintains a worldwide presence in the major diamond trading centers.
<b>Bold text</b>
</description>
<properties>
<property>18k White Gold</property>
<property>Conflict Free diamonds</property>
<property>100% natural diamonds</property>
</properties>
</product>

<product id="2" category="Necklaces">
<title>14K Gold 12-15mm Australian South Sea White Pearl Necklace - AAA Quality, 51cm Length </title>
<price>99999</price>
<image>necklace1.jpg</image>
<stock>89</stock>
<description>Meticulously crafted in 750 Gold, this exclusive design by NATURAL DIAMOND is available to you directly from the source. The 'Matthiola' design is set with 47 diamonds, weighing 2.22 ctw. Featuring a sparkly 1.57ct center stone, graded F / VS1 natural diamond this beautiful piece is available in 14K gold, 18K gold or platinum.

Read below to learn about the quality of the main diamond:

F Color:
This F color diamond has no color visible to an untrained eye. As the least expensive diamond color in the colorless range (D-F) F color diamonds display minimal color difference from D or E color diamonds and offer a lower price.

VS1 Clarity:
This VS1 clarity diamond has few, very small inclusions. Inclusions are not visible to the unaided eye.

Round Shape:
The Round Brilliant cut diamond is the most popular diamond shape available today. In addition to being the most popular shape, a Round diamond gives you more flexibility in terms of balancing cut, color, and clarity grades while still getting the fire and brilliance you want.

EGL Certificate:
EGL certificates are recognized around the globe for their accuracy and integrity, defining industry standards in evaluation and appraisal. The company maintains a worldwide presence in the major diamond trading centers.
<b>Bold text</b>
</description>
<properties>
<property>High quality 14K gold clasp</property>
<property>Every item is packaeged and shipped in a beautiful jewelry gift box</property>
<property>Certificate of authenticity</property>
</properties>
</product>

<product id="3" category="Rings">
<title>18ct White Gold 1 Carat Certified G/VS Round Brilliant Diamond Engagement Ring - Size K</title>
<price>99999</price>
<image>ring2.jpg</image>
<stock>100</stock>
<description>Perfect for the woman who wants a classic style with a twist, this solitaire diamond ring offers a striking and pretty variation on a simple four-claw style.

A wonderful choice to mark an engagement, this style is classic enough to be beautiful forever but will delight the recipient with its pretty design details. It will also sit seamlessly with a straight wedding band.

<b>Bold text</b>
</description>
<properties>
<property>Beautiful ring made from 18ct White Gold</property>
<property>Set with a solitaire 1.00ct diamond</property>
<property>Designed to be a pretty twist on a classic style</property>
</properties>
</product> 

<product id="4" category="Bracelets">
<title>Modern 9 ct Gold Bracelet - 20cm*3mm, 13 Grams</title>
<price>99999</price>
<image>bracelet1.jpg</image>
<stock>100</stock>
<description>Beautiful 9ct and 18ct Gold in Fine designs. Take a look at our rings, pendants and earring sets, all in a variety of colours and shapes with solitaires and clusters, diamonds and gemstones. Hallmarked in the UK and hand polished for the ultimate comfort and finesse. 
<b>Bold text</b>
</description>
<properties>
<property>30 Day Satisfaction Guarantee</property>
<property>Stylish design</property>
<property>Quality craftsmanship</property>
</properties>
</product> 

<product id="5" category="Bracelets">
<title>Vs 2.00Ct Round Diamond Solitaire Pendant 14K Gold</title>
<price>99999</price>
<image>necklace2.jpg</image>
<stock>100</stock>
<description>Also available in 18k white, yellow or rose gold. A great value and a pendant she will cherish for the rest of her life. This excellent quality pendant containins a round-cut solitaire VS diamond in a bezel setting made of solid 14k gold. Our master goldsmiths fabricate this item to our specifications, and then choose a natural bright white diamond, of high colour and clarity to finish this magnificent piece. Capture her heart as the diamond captures the light and shows its fiery brilliance. When you buy from LureDiamonds you are joining the thousands of worldwide customers who no longer pay too much for their fine jewellery needs. A chain is also available, as well as your choice of gold colour and upgrades all the way to platinum! 
<b>Bold text</b>
</description>
<properties>
<property>All the best designs with new items constantly being added</property>
<property>Only high quality stones</property>
<property>Great value</property>
</properties>
</product> 
 
<product id="6" category="Earrings">
<title>Round Cut, Diamond Earrings in 18K Gold / White</title>
<price>99999</price>
<image>Earring1.jpg</image>
<stock>88</stock>
<description>Meticulously crafted in 750 Gold, this exclusive design by NATURAL DIAMOND is available to you directly from the source. The 'Violet' design is set with 2 diamonds, weighing 4.01 ctw. Featuring sparkly 2.00ct and 2.01ct main diamonds, graded K / SI2 natural diamond this beautiful piece is available in 14K or 18K gold. If you love the design but prefer a different center stone or would like to have a different design with the same center stone please contact us anytime to receive more options.
<b>Bold text</b>
</description>
<properties>
<property>100% Natural Diamond</property>
<property>Conflict Free Diamonds</property>
<property>Certificate of authenticity</property>
</properties>
</product> 

<product id="7" category="Rings">
<title>Round Cut, Solitaire Diamond Ring in 18K Gold</title>
<price>99999</price>
<image>Ring3.jpg</image>
<stock>100</stock>
<description>Meticulously crafted in 750 Gold, this exclusive design by NATURAL DIAMOND is available to you directly from the source. The 'Tritoma' design is set with 107 diamonds, weighing 2.61 ctw. Featuring a sparkly 2.01ct center stone, graded E / VS1 natural diamond this beautiful piece is available in 14K gold, 18K gold or platinum.
<b>Bold text</b>
</description>
<properties>
<property>750 Gold</property>
<property>Conflict Free Diamonds</property>
<property>100% natural diamonds</property>
</properties>
</product>   
 
</products>
